<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My weird vlog</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My weird vlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:02:12 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:02:12 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Who the fuck am I?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a weird guy that has a doubtable fascination of having&#xA;the control of everything. Thus I am aimed to be an embedded&#xA;systems engineer focusing on biomedical engineering because I&#xA;wanted to be a biologist and a scientist when I was a kid but&#xA;my parents fucked up everything as it&amp;rsquo;s tradition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I like to make things, I don&amp;rsquo;t like to take courses because&#xA;in my geography happen that the teachers on technology subjects&#xA;are stupid boomers with no idea about what they are doing. Note&#xA;that my country has an educative system that award the ignorance&#xA;and summision over knowledge and skills. If you happen to see&#xA;skilled people is always on boring stuff focused on making&#xA;short term money. You would think that is ok if they need it, but&#xA;even on abundance they do the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>001 Start</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/001-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 01:13:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/001-start/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-beggining-of-my-vlog&#34;&gt;The beggining of my vlog&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Idk what to sayl I&amp;rsquo;m just starting this Hugo website because I&#xA;have so much to say and there is so much absence of smart&#xA;people in my life that I need somewhere to share my coding&#xA;adventures and talking shit about windows, web dev, stupid&#xA;people, VS code users, platform IO users, internet users, oxygen&#xA;users and so, like a Twitter but actually interesting and with bit&#xA;manipulation included and a superiority condition that u cannot&#xA;claim to be false.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
